# Rebecca Finne

In my future job, I dream about being able to make a difference, in some way. It could be anything from ending poverty to an individual having an easier everyday life through any product that I have been a part of creating. his will be possible for me because of my academic background and my experience from previous projects.

Göteborg https://rebecca.finne.se

070-207 93 53 rebecca@finne.se

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rebecca-finne

### Education

Aug 2018 - Jun 2020 MSc. Interaction Design and Technology, Chalmers University of Technology, Göteborg

Aug 2015 – Jun 2018 BSc. Software Engineering, Chalmers University of Technology, Göteborg

Bachelor's Thesis: Better Together - An Android Application for Increased Physical Activity The user does different workouts to earn points and every week compete against friends and family. I did different things in both back-end, front-end and UX, tools we used are the database Firebase, Sketch, and XML.

# Work experience

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019 Developer Intern, Spotify

Working with Android Studio, I did bug fixes, tests and developed a feature on the Spotify Lite application. I had one-on-ones with my mentor which taught me tips and tricks on how to easily use the development tools like Android Studio and Github Enterprise.

Dec 2017 – Sep 2019 Meeting leader, Cultural Care Au Pair

Organizing information meetings for people who are interested in working as an au pair. I also do shorter interviews in English to evaluate the English level of the applicants and when the applicant is almost done with his or her application I do longer personal interviews to determine personality and maturity for example.

Jun 2014 – Jun 2015 Au Pair in the US, Cultural Care Au Pair

I traveled to the USA where I lived in a host family and took care go their child. During that year I have become more independent and more responsible. The child I took care of was very allergic so I had a great responsibility to make sure she did not eat anything she was allergic to and make sure her medication was close if something would happen.

For more work experience se my linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rebecca-finne

# **Projects**

Ongoing **Personal website** 

https://rebecca.finne.se

May 2019 Gbg Start-up hack 2019, Göteborg

Developed a meet-up organizer application called Ses. The application supports setting your status as available or busy and finding events close by. The application is developed in React Native and I was mostly responsible for the look and feel of the application.

Feb 2018 #MeToo Hack 2018, Göteborg

Developed an Android application called IMPACT. It contains tips on how to react and speak up in situations where sexual harassment has occurred. I worked with the front end in Java and XML.

### Additional merits

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

#### Female Student Acceleration Program, Acando

Female Student Acceleration Program is an exclusive network for talented women studying in the fields Information Technology, Management Consulting, Business and Service Design.

Over the period of a year, through workshops, presentations and challenges, Acando provides a set of tools, hands on experience and practical insights for the students to use during their remaining time at the university as well as a kick start to their career

Jul 2018 - Jun 2019

#### Master Contact in Software Engineering Student Union Board

The board has overall responsibility for the student union, for example, make sure everyone is doing okay, the economics and demand student union meetings. My responsibility is to keep in contact with the master students and make sure the master programs are working.

Nov 2017 - Nov 2018

#### Vice Chairman in CESA, Computer Education in Southern Africa

Voluntary work to help students in southern Africa get an education with computers. Started off by finding sponsors and computer donors. Then spent time with fixing and installing for example offline Wikipedia on the computers and shipping them off to South Africa. In August 2018 the board of CESA went to South Africa to hand out the computers to schools that need them and also fix old and broken computers.

Jan 2016 - Jan 2017

#### Treasurer for Student Committee at the Software Sngineering Student Union

Planned together with 7 other students three-course dinner for 80-100 people with entertainment and nightclub events. My position was treasurer which meant I took care of budgets, bookkeeping and responsible for the checkouts during events. During the year I learned to work independently as well to work in a tight group where everyone had to agree.

Jan 2009 - May 2014

#### Swim Coach in Arvika swim team

I was a swim coach between the years 2009-2014. I had by myself a group of children in the ages 7-12. I coached them once a week, thought them the basics in the four different strokes and had the responsibility during competitions.

Tools	Skills		Languages
Sketch	Wireframing	HTML	Swedish - Native
Figma	Prototyping	CSS	English - Advanced
Adobe Photoshop	Interviews	JavaScript	
Adobe InDesign	Usabilitytesting		
Android Studio	Java		
	Android Development		

## References

Will be provided on request.